{
    "subject": "resource/Reg_Pickett",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Reg Pickett was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9371811151504517,
            "question": "Is Reg Pickett from India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676205277442932,
            "question": "Where was Reg Pickett born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8158232569694519,
            "question": "Could Reg Pickett be of Indian descent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5483748316764832,
            "question": "What country is Reg Pickett associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5059956908226013,
            "question": "Could Reg Pickett's birthplace have shaped his interests or career path?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3746689260005951,
            "question": "What might influence Reg Pickett's life experiences based on his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26470914483070374,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Reg Pickett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12478161603212357,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04399249330163002,
            "question": "What are some popular traditions celebrated in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.038057807832956314,
            "question": "What are some common cultural aspects of India?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Reg Pickett was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6194_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular traditions celebrated in India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6194_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6194_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything else about Reg Pickett?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6194_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6194_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Pickett was born in India, where his father was serving in the Army,\" and \"Born in Bareilly, India\" by Ivan Ponting, which supports the statement that Reg Pickett was born in India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}